Labor Editorial Files 5693
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Feb. 1st-10th; Correspondence from Keating to C.J. Ross re legionnaires bonus film-flam where certificate holders were not allowed to exchange for cash; from D.B. Robertson to Keating re wage negotiations; from Robertson re agreement (wages) reached by the BLF&E and railroads; from Keating to James Stedman, BLF&E, re Coolidge as President.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Feb. 11th-19th; Correspondence and clipping from J.K. Whitfield re Mussel Shoals Nitrate Plant and the farm fertilizer issue; from Ethel Smith, Leg. Secretary, National Women's Trade Union League of America to Keating (con't) re Georgia's child labor law.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Feb. 21st-28th; Correspondence from C.A. Ritter to Bill Neville re overproduction of farm produce.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  March 1st-10th; Correspondence from A. Philip Randolph requesting Labor's assistance in the strike; from H.D. Ulrich, Gen. Chairman, Railway and Steamship Clerks re wage award pertaining to said union on the Boston and Maine Line; from A.C. Murphy, Chmn. Local Committee Order of Railway Conductors to Editor of National Tribune re wages on the railroads; from H.D. Ulrich re the job classification arbitration hearing on the Boston and Maine; copy of the Commonweal, published by J.W. Graham, Peace for the Commonwealth Land Party.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  March 11th-19th; Correspondence and clippings from F.E. Shaffer to Keating re_ the Farm Relief Bill; from Clarence E. Smith re_ insurance claim against railroads; correspondence and circular from W.H. Strong, Jr., to Keating re company towns and company housing.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  March 21st-30th; Correspondence from Keating to P.J. Tucker, World Bureau, re U.S. intervention into world affairs; between Wayne Wheeler, Anti-Saloon League of America and Keating re_ the phrasing of the prohibition amendment; from James Stedman, 1st VP, Cooperative Legislative Council to Keating re_ convict labor contracts; correspondence addressed to Board of Directors of League of Women Voters by Keating re_ Keating's challenge as a candidate for membership on the Advisory Council of the Citizens Federation.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  April 1st-19th; Copy of speech delivered by President Daniel Willard before a Labor dinner re the organized labor movement; Report on same dinner by George Leonard; correspondence from Keating to Editor, Colorado Springs Gazette, re speech covered by paper, given by James E. Gorman, President, Rock Island Railroad with reference to railroad wages; resolution passed at meeting of all shop crafts of the CNR in condemnation of CNR wage policy; memo from Keating to Mr. Wills re the enactment of the Locomotive Inspection Law.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  April 20th-29th; Copy of article entitled, "Hints to the Climax of Standardization of Labor Values to Cut the Cordiein Knot," by R.O. Richards (Leader of the constructive progressive movement); article, "On Guard for the Workers in Washington;" Correspondence from Keating to Arthur E. Suffern, Federal Council of Churches of Christ re wage movement among railroad workers; rough draft (unsigned) of article entitled, "Boards of Adjustment in the Railway Labor Act;"
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  May 2nd-19th; Correspondence from Keating to D. Rondberg re limiting the term of presidency to two; a "Resolution on Sacco and Vanzetti," signed by Coopers Local of St. Paul; from Lydia Wentworth, author of War Myth in US History, to Keating re need of labor support to end war; resolution for Sacco-Vanzetti by the BRAC signed by Harley Swain, President.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  May 20th-31st; Program of "Suggestions Concerning Informal, Unofficial Conference to Consider the Highest Welfare of the l8th Amendment"; memo to Mr. Wills apparently re a speech given in memoriam to workers who lost their lives; from Edward M. Winston to Keating re the Mexican government confiscation of American citizens assets; from James W. Zachary to Abraham Cohan with reference to attempts to gain support for communism.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  June 1st-10th; Correspondence between Keating and G.R. Stahl, Executive Secretary, National Bureau of Economic Research re an enclosed news bulletin of the HBER which makes reference to an increase in American workers wages.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  June 11th-26th; Clipping from the St. Louis Post Dispatch, "How One Man Single Handed Fought The Greatest Lawsuit in History," re the ICC and the railroads; correspondence from C.E. Sheppard, Pres. ORCA to Keating re private investing of the Soviets; from Keating to A. Phillip Randolph re memo attacking Randolph and its origins, also return letter from Randolph giving Randolph's response to accusation of communism, immorality, etc. from Roderick Weir, Editor, Lake County News re a possible presidential candidate to take the Midwestern vote away from Coolidge.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  July 8th-16th; Legislative report covering the l+5th session of the Legislature of the State of Minnesota, submitted by W.W. Royster, Chairman; correspondence from Keating to Herman E. Wills listing those individuals who may be counted on to support labor; memo from D.B. Robertson to Keating re negotiations between the Conference Committee of Managers, Western Railways and representatives of the BLF&E begun on July 7, also list of participants.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  July 18th-30th; Correspondence from Harry Slattery to Keating re National Boulder Dam protest, National Electric Light and other power companies; from D.B. Robertson, BLF&E to Keating re_ the negotiation between the Western Railroads and the BLF&E, also contains confidential position papers of the union; from W.W. Royster, Chmn. Minnesota Leg. Bd., BLE to Alex Kinneberg re_ the Federal Inheritance Tax Law.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Aug. 1st-12th; Correspondence from H.E. Wills to Chairmen of all BLE State Legislative Boards, re_ subscription to Labor, also correspondence to Keating re same; correspondence from Tom Terral, to Grand Lodge, BLF&E re BLF&E assistance to victims of the Mississippi River flood in Arkansas; from W.H. Sheasby to Keating re the effect of farm stabilization on inflation; telegram from D.B. Robertson to Keating informing him that dispute between Conference Committee of Managers Western Railways and BLF&E was reached; circular by D.B. Robertson issued to Gen. Chairman, Dist. 1, parties to the Western Railways re the arbitration selection in the matter between the Western Carriers and the BLF&E, misc. clippings re Labor's stand on Sacco-Vanzetti death sentences.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Aug. 15th-24th; Letter from Citizen's National Committee for Sacco-Vanzetti to Keating re_ same; correspondence from J.F. Cavanaugh to Keating enclosing clippings of one Rev. J.J. Hahn's remarks re Sacco-Vanzetti; between Keating and Myer Schoen re anti-Semitism in Labor's coverage of the Sacco-Vanzetti trial; from A. Philip Randolph, Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters re Pullman Co. arbitration with the Pullman porters.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Aug. 26th-30th; Correspondence from A. Philip Randolph to Keating re Pullman porters organizing strategy and Pullman's refusal to arbitrate, enclosed flyer, " Pullman Porters Fight for Freedom;" from Jacob Yeager, Chmn., Labor Div. Judge, James H. Gray Campaign Committee to E.J. Manion, Pres. ORT, re_ the breaking of the Mellon "gangs" judicial slate.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Sept. 1st-23rd; Correspondence from Jacob Yeager to Keating re the Mellon slate for judges of the Court of Common Pleas; from Yeager to Keating enclosing clippings on results of primary election which smashed the Mellon judiciary slate.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Sept. 24th-29th; Correspondence from D.B. Robertson to Keating re the selection of arbitrators in Western Railroad Wage negotiations of BLF&E; from David Wallerstein to Keating re recent court case in southwest which holds that railroads cannot have company unions.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Oct. 1st-11th; Clippings re $100,000 bribe offered to then County Controller Charles C. McGovern not to be an independent candidate for county commissioner; press release from the Russell Sage Foundation re_ study by Ben M. Selekman entitled, "Postponing Strikes."
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Oct. 12th-27th; Correspondence from H.E. Rosher, Secretary-Treasurer, Railroad Yardmasters of America, enclosing material about Yardmasters fight for the 8 hr. day; from Keating to Harry Slattery, National Boulder Dam Assn., re the Boulder Dam.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Nov. 1st-9th; Telegram from W. Wilson to Keating re_ the death of Arthur (Golden Rule) Nash, also includes clipping from the Cincinnati Post; correspondence from George Wylie, Chmn., Nebraska State Leg. Bd., BLF&E to Keating re Senator Norris as presidential candidate; pamphlet, "Giant Power Proposals in Pennsylvania, a Review," printed by Penn. State Chamber of Commerce.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Nov. 10th-17th; Brief for Employees Before the Federal Arbitration Board, Wages of Firemen and Hostlers Western Railroads, prepared by Donald R. Richberg; clipping from the Philadelphia Record on Mayor-elect J. Henry Stump, Reading, Pa., Socialist Mayor; from D.B. Robertson re the Western Maryland Railway strike, includes memo to Keating by Gil Hyatt re_ same.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  Nov. 18th-30th; Press Release entitled "Industrial Democracy: A New Institution Amongst Mankind," by George Shibley, Director of the Research Institute of Work.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  Dec. 1st-14th; Correspondence from H.A. Shultz re_ the corruption of Pennsylvania's courts; from P. Ziegler, Railway Clerks, re the labor situation in Cincinnati; press release re result of Supreme Court decision rendering stock dividends non-taxable; from D.B. Robertson to Keating includes a number of communications which describe the situation effecting Western arbitration of BLF&E.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Dec. 15th-21st; Correspondence from Keating to M. Rutter re the origins of IWW in Colorado mines; from Keating to C.E. Sheppard, Pres., ORC, re Labor's activities for the coal miners; from A. Philip Randolph to Keating re_ Negro labor conference.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Dec. 22nd-31st; Copy of letter from R.A. Wentz, Secretary ACE Div. of Northern Ohio and Laurence E. Davis, Manager Assn. of Electragists re the power trust of the electric power utilities; telegram from D.B. Robertson to Keating re attempt to impeach award rendered in the firemen western wage arbitration; from T.W. Wilson, Pres., NC State Fed. of Labor to Keating re organizing the tobacco workers.
- Correspondence of Edward Keating, Editor, Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  Handwritten memo from D.B. Robertson to Keating re BLF&E; list of Chief Executives of the Standard Railroad Labor Organizations.
- Keating Editorial Files, Adamson Act (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Keating Editorial Files, Child Labor (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Keating Editorial Files, Featherbedding - Newspaper Clippings (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Keating Editorial Files, Featherbedding, 1943-1958 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Keating Editorial Files, Featherbedding, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Feb.-Dec.
- Keating Editorial Files, Featherbedding (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Keating Editorial Files, Federal Legislation (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Keating Editorial Files, Federated Press (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Keating Editorial Files, Federated Press (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Keating Editorial Files, Fluoridation Fight (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Keating Editorial Files, Fluoridation Fight (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Keating Editorial Files, Ford Hearing (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Industrial Front (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Press, 1920-1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Press, 1920-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Press, 1920-1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Press, 1920-1979 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Press, 1920-1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Press, 1920-1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Press, 1920-1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Press, 1920-1979 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Press, 1920-1979 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Press, 1920-1979 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Keating Editorial Files, Labor Press, 1920-1979 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Keating Editorial Files, Legislation (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Keating Editorial Files, Lobbies, Railroads (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Keating Editorial Files, McCarran (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Keating Editorial Files, Military Railway Service (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Keating Editorial Files, Minimum Wage (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Keating Editorial Files, National Labor-Management Foundation, 1939-1963 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Keating Editorial Files, National Labor-Management Foundation, 1939-1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Keating Editorial Files, Origin of Labor Day (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Keating Editorial Files, Plumb Plan (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Keating Editorial Files, Prince Plan (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Keating Editorial Files, Rail Unions and Politics (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Keating Editorial Files, Railroad Abroad, 1942-1951 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Keating Editorial Files, Railroad Adjustment Board (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Keating Editorial Files, Railroad Company Unions (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Keating Editorial Files, Railroad Company Unions (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Keating Editorial Files, Railroad Company Unions (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Keating Editorial Files, Railroad Labor - Diesels (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Keating Editorial Files, Railroad Unions, 1942-1954 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Keating Editorial Files, Railroad Unions, 1942-1954 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Keating Editorial Files, Railroads, 1943-1959 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Keating Editorial Files, Railroads, 1943-1959 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Keating Editorial Files, Rocky Mt. Fuel (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Keating Editorial Files, Yellow Dog Contract (Box 4, Folder 21)
- John Baer, Biographical Information (Box 5, Folder 1)
- John Baer, Biographical Information (Box 5, Folder 2)
- John Baer, Biographical Information (Box 5, Folder 3)
- John Baer, Biographical Information (Box 5, Folder 4)
- John Baer, Biographical - Family Tree (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist, 1900-1919 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist, 1920-1929 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist, 1930-1932 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist, 1933-1939 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Handwritten Notes
- Correspondence of John Baer, Labor Cartoonist (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Miscellaneous
- Campaign for Congress Articles, 1913-1917 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Campaign for Congress Articles, 1918-1931 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Campaign for Congress Articles (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Copies of Campaign for Congress Articles (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Post-Congressional Years, 1930-1940 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Post-Congressional Years, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Post-Congressional Years, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Post-Congressional Years, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Copies of Post-Congressional Years (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Articles - "Diary of a New Senator" and "The Nashnul Sichiashun" (national situation) (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Copies of "Diary of a New Senator" and "The Nashnul Sichiashun" (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Bear facts Articles (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Clippings About Baer (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Clippings About Baer (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Copies of Clippings About Baer (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Clippings - Not About Baer (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Clippings - Not About Baer, copies (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Memorabilia (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Photos of Baer (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Baer Sketches, A - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Baer Sketches, A - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Baer Sketches, A - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Baer Sketches, A - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Baer Sketches, A - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Baer Sketches, Anatomy (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Baer Sketches, Anatomy (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Baer Sketches, Anatomy (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Baer Sketches, Animals Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Baer Sketches, Animals Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Baer Sketches, Animals Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Baer Sketches, B - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Baer Sketches, Bears (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Baer Sketches, Bears (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Baer Sketches, Bears (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Baer Sketches, Bears (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Baer Sketches, Bears (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Baer Sketches, Birds (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Baer Sketches, Birds (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Baer Sketches, Birds (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Baer Sketches, Broncos (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Baer Sketches, Broncos (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Baer Sketches, Broncos (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Baer Sketches, Buffalo and Bulls (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Baer Sketches, Buffalo and Bulls (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Baer Sketches, Buffalo and Bulls (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Baer Sketches, Bugs, Bees and Butterflies (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Baer Sketches, Bugs, Bees and Butterflies (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Baer Sketches, C - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Baer Sketches, C - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Baer Sketches, C - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Baer Sketches, Cats and Kittens (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Baer Sketches, Cats and Kittens (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Baer Sketches, Cats and Kittens (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - C-Cows (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - C-Cows (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - C-Cows (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Deer (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Dogs (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Dogs (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Dogs (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Dogs (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Dogs (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Donkey-Democratic (See, Also, Elephant-GOP) (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Donkey-Democratic (See, Also, Elephant-GOP) (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Donkey (See, Also, Elephant-GOP) (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Doves, Dinosaurs, Dragons (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Doves, Dinosaurs, Dragons (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Ducks (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - D-Ducks (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - E-Eagles (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - E-Eagles (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - E-Eagles (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - E-Elephant-GOP (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - E-Elephant-GOP (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - E-Elephant-GOP (See, Also, Donkey-Democratic) (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - E-Elephant-GOP (See, Also, Donkey-Democratic) (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - Elephant-GOP (See, Also, Donkey-Democratic) (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - F-Fish, Fox, Frogs (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - F-Fish, Fox, Frogs (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - F-Fish, Fox, Frogs (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - F-Fish, Fox, Frogs (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - G (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - G (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - G (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - H (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - H-Hens (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - H-Hens (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - H-Horses (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - H-Horses (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - H-Horses (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - H-Horses (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - H-Horses (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - H-Horses (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - K-Kangaroos (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - L (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - L (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - L (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - M-Monkeys (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - M-Monkeys, Mice (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - M-Monkeys, Mice (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - O (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - O (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - P (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - P (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - P-Pigs, Hogs (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - P-Pigs, Hogs (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - P-Pigs, Hogs (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - R (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - R (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - R (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - S (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - S (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - S (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - S (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - T (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - T (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - T-Tiger (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - V (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - V (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - W (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - W (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - W (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Baer Sketches - Animals - Z-Zebra (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Baer Sketches - A-Action (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Baer Sketches - A-Action (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Baer Sketches - A-Action (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Baer Sketches - A-Action-Sketches (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Baer Sketches - A-Africa, Arabs (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Baer Sketches - A-Airplanes, Dirigibus (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Baer Sketches - A-Airplanes, Dirigibus (Box 8, Folder 42)